bewebmedia.com 2010-07-26

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  

**BeWebMedia is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.**  
The BeWebMedia website and BeWebMedia ad serving technology are owned by BeWebCom Corporation. They are operated by BeWebCom Corporation and/or its subsidiaries and/or affiliates companies in the United States and worldwide. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. This Privacy Statement is intended to provide you notice of BeWebMedia’s information management practices, including all types of information gathered, how it is used and safeguarded, and the degree to which you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information. Herewith you find the information regarding BeWebMedia's commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

**Consumer Information**  
BeWebMedia uses its own technology to serve ads at this site and/or at its direct publishers network and/or at publishers connected via third party ad server. In the course of delivering an ad to you, our ad server may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**  
BeWebMedia respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personally identifiable information that you provide in connection with your use of its Web sites and Services.

**User Account**  
In order to use our Advertisers’ and/or Publishers’ platform, you need to register us. As Publisher you may register directly from this website. As Advertiser you need to contact BeWebMedia operator in order to create your account. You will be asked to provide certain personal information and other information about you and your business, such as your company name, your name, your address, your telephone number, e-mail address and any other information needed to complete the registration form. Any and all information provided will not be available to the general public while you participate in some Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in such Services. You are also responsible for maintaining and updating the registration information in your User Account with current and complete information. You can also send an e-mail to request deactivation of your User Account.

**Cookies and Opt Out**  
Like most Internet sites, BeWebMedia its own ad serving uses "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. Neither BeWebMedia nor any other third party ad serving party, if any linked to BeWebMedia, uses these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.

**What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience?**  
A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer. For instance, cookies help ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested. Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web (by not repeatedly serving the same ads to you and delivering more relevant messages to you).

**Opt out**  
If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you may click here.

**Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy**  
BeWebMedia is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the IAB (Interactive Advertising Bureau). If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact our Customer Services .We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as BeWebMedia may update it from time to time.
